How to download and import animation from Mixamo?
How to download animation from Mixamo and import it into the software?
We will export and upload the customized virtual model to Mixamo.
After the upload and binding is done, we need to download the model of T-Pose first.
After downloading the model of T-Pose, we can choose the animation we need,
then select the settings we need to download the animation file.
Import the FBX file into Marvelous Designer,
click the bottom triangle and check the key animation in the animation editor to see if it is correctly imported.
All videos are imported with the following options.
Now we choose the animation value of this animation,
and it will appear in the Motion folder.
Finally, we create a new project,
import the T-Pose virtual model that was downloaded before,
and then import the saved animation.
When importing, click to move to the beginning,
and click to switch to the first motion.
Now the T-Pose moved to the beginning of the animation will automatically appear.
Thank you.